Within the Clover's fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
Asta, born unable to harness mana, was granted the power of anti-magic from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members of Spade Kingdom's Dark Triad also possessed powers from the devils of the Underworld,
and used them to launch an evasion on the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from his belief in himself and from the support of his friends,
Asta continues to fight for the safety of this world.
Upon returning to his home village of Hajj,
Yuno was introduced to a mysterious man from the Spade Kingdom named Ralph.
Lord Yuno, our nation's future is in your hands.
You belong to the royal house of Grin Berial.
It's Sion, the prince and rightful heir to the Spade Kingdom's throne.
Ralph revealed the truth about Yuno's birth.
Just then, Yuno received word that the Golden Dawn headquarters was under attack.
Even so, I am also Yuno of the Clover Kingdom.
The perpetrators were two Spade Kingdom mages, named Goderoy and Foil.
Only a select few were good enough to get powers from the Dark Triad,
and we were at the top of the list.
We're the Dark Disciples.
All of us are stage zero mages.
They were led by Xenon of the Dark Triad, who was possessed by a devil.
And their gold will soon clear.
World Tree Magic. Magic Warding Ash!
So that's World Tree Magic, is it?
Our side could certainly use that.
I'll be taking you with me.
Bone Magic. Eternal Fang.
Eternal Fang.
By the time Yuno arrived at the Golden Dawn Headquarters.
I'm here!
A grim tragedy had already unfolded.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
To my comrades!
We're gonna wake you in for the brand new world.
Yeah!
We're gonna take you to the brand new world.
To the brand new world!
We're gonna wake you in for the brand new world.
Get your hands up, baby!
We're gonna take you to the brand new world.
Oh, yeah!
They burned out!
Get it on! Get it on! 始めよう!
難航不楽のリアリティー!
立ち止まる時間はないさ!
Hold on! Hold on!
Yeah!
Now this time, fight for liberty!
真実性!
飲み込む常識!
Overwave!
逆境の先にある朝!
Oh, yeah!
幻想に埋もらえた人生の夢!
Hands up!
Shout it! Shout it! Loud up!
Yes! Do it! Do it! Start it!
Never give up!
限界を超えても
加速していくスピリット!
We can't face!
Let's go home!
Believe in myself!
衝動的に突き進め!
Don't be afraid!
誰よりも高く飛べ!
Take it to the sky!
想像を超えた世界をこの手に!
The ground up!
想像せよ!
偽りのない自分の道!
Yes! It's a ground up!
Hey, yeah!
Believe in myself!
Believe in yourself!
Hey, yeah!
When you came to the Golden Dawn, some of our squad looked down on you for being a commoner.
They resented you and were jealous of your powers, and I was no exception.
How can you stand up for people like us, given the way we've behaved?
We're comrades. I don't need another reason. Just that I care.
Apologies.
When we're finished, let's all go out to eat together.
Hey, come back!
You know.
You're invited. In fact, we specifically invited you.
Oh, I didn't.
Hammond knows some great restaurants around the Royal Capital.
Yeah, we thought it might be fun to hit the town with the whole squad and party.
Hey!
Don't you go getting a big head just because you moved all the way up to Vice Captain in only 18 months.
Yeah, you better watch it.
I'll try.
Oh, you got an attitude?
That's it. You're about to get the noogie to end all noogies.
Yuno, you've been smiling a lot more recently, huh?
Mm-hmm.
It's a good look for you, though.
Excuse me?
I'm the only one who's allowed to pay that much attention to Yuno's gorgeous face, and don't you forget it!
Yuno!
We must've killed about half, and the rest ain't far behind.
Well, at least they died fighting a strong opponent, right?
I think they should feel honored!
Win spirit magic!
Spirit Storm!
Ah, so you've been chosen by the wind spirit, eh?
How about that?
But since my stone magic techniques are enhanced by devil power, they're tougher than iron or steel!
So your spells won't scratch me!
Monosome, spirits hushed dance!
He's attacking me and protecting his wounded friends at the same time!
That arcane stage captain should be fighting Lord Xenon right now!
Well, well!
Didn't think anyone below the captain would be zero stage!
It looks like things are finally getting interesting here!
My name's Goderoy, kid!
Now what's yours?
You don't need to know my name!
You're my enemy!
Don't be like that!
I want us to get acquainted!
Before I kill ya!
Tell me!
Why are you doing this?
Beats me!
Just following orders!
Only thing I know is the Dark Triad is looking to snap up an arcane stage fighter!
And as long as I get to have some fun, that's good enough for me!
Arcane stage?
Ah, now let me tell ya, these guys are a riot!
They killed that softy of a king we had,
and then gave even more power to those of us who were looking for some action!
The former king was a fool!
Might is always right!
Cause when you're strong, you get to make your own rules!
You're insane!
How does somebody enjoy making people suffer?
Are you even capable of human emotions?
Hmm?
Of course!
Nothing's more human than the incredible rush you feel when you kill somebody!
I'm hooked on it, I tell ya!
And you're a tough guy like me!
So you understand!
Let's get one thing straight!
I am nothing like you!
Win spirit creation magic!
Spirit of Zephyr!
Hey, that's not a bad trick!
But you're no match for me, little man!
Might as well quit!
I think I understand.
The reason this world is so screwed up is people like you!
Like me?
That's the way it's been since the dawn of time!
What are you rambling about?
My stone magic!
He's canceling it out instantly!
Whether I'm a Clover Kingdom Mage!
Or a Spade Kingdom Prince!
Either way!
I have to cut you down!
Whether I'm a Clover Kingdom mage, or a Spade Kingdom Prince, either way...
I have to cut you down.
This spell has enormous range. I have no way of knowing where the enemy is.
I have to admit, I'm impressed that your magic is so solid.
Steel Magic Blazing Spiral Blast!
It's too bad, though.
No matter how sturdy it may be, it isn't capable of doing any damage against me.
I'm getting tired of playing with you, so it's time to die.
Ready?
I'm a Zero Stage Mage, a genius who was specifically selected by the Dark Triad.
Even if there was a whole army of you amateurs, you'd never be able to stop me!
How are they so much more powerful than us?
He's not even the leader, and his magic's on par with the Captain's!
There's something suspicious about their abilities.
My squad mates are low on mana. If I don't do something, we'll all be wiped out. But I can't even track where he is!
Useless North isn't responding to his mist magic, and another Atlas is already at maximum size.
Some of the elves' magic still dwells within us. I'm sure those who were possessed would like to renounce it after the suffering it caused our people.
But I disagree with that. We should take their strength, and use it as a force for good, to protect our great kingdom.
I'm not as strong as an elf, but after six months, I've made that power my own.
Even so, I'm no match for someone like him!
Your magic and your body are completely worn down. You should surrender.
You seem smart, so surely you must have enough intelligence to understand that you can't possibly survive this battle.
You've weakened me physically. But you'll never break my will.
Then will yourself to die, you piece of trash!
Klaus, I'm here to help you!
You know...
He just blew my mist away. He might be a worthy foe. Almost.
Mist creation magic, sealing spectral hands!
I'm still wounded from that last fight.
You look tired. Are you sure you can do it?
Come at me! Every last one of you! You're all as good as dead!
Thanks to Yuno, I can see where you are now.
I'll move myself, and another Atlas, breaking your illusionary armor!
You subhuman scum!
He's severely injured. How is he able to keep on moving?
Every time I face someone who's naturally skilled like he is, I have the same thought.
I worry that I may never surpass their abilities, no matter how much intense training I undergo.
But I've learned how to handle that insecurity.
I've just got to keep breaking through those walls!
How do I keep on moving?
I've trained for this exact moment.
It's over. You know. Er, Vice-Captain you know. Thank you.
It was nothing, sir.
You don't need to be so formal. You outrank me now. You're the second in command.
Hearing you call me Vice-Captain feels weird. Just use my name. It's easier.
Honestly, I couldn't care less.
Well, I do care, thank you! You know the Vice-Captain, which means that he's almost at the top!
And do you know who was there for him every step of the way?
That's right! It was yours truly! His ultra-cute right-hand lady!
A.K.A. the greatest partner in the whole wide world!
Right, my darling?
There's a big difference between Captain and Vice-Captain.
Aw, you're always so modest!
Owie!
What is that mana?
He took down Captain Vongions!
It can't be!
Who the hell is that?!
Owie!
Oh dear. It looks like we left a few of you alive.
You must be...
I see Gauderoy and Foyum have been defeated.
Those two are only at 40% power.
I suppose I shouldn't have bothered bringing them if they couldn't surpass halfway.
Yuno! Hurry, a new spirit die!
This guy... he's serious!
There's no time to dodge it!
He's too strong!
What should we do?
Really?
You okay, Klaus?
Oh!
You bastard!
The spirit of Zephyr won't work?
Wait, it's worse than that!
He's regenerating himself extremely quickly!
It's stage zero. Well then, let me show you.
A bit of my Devil's power.
55%.
Do you see what your problem is?
But isn't that your weak? I'm just that much better.
All of this... is for the glory of the Spade Kingdom.
The destruction of Spade Kingdom!
Wait, this is...
Prince Yudo!
Please, Yudo! Don't leave me! I can't live without you!
The Prince...
He's dead?
No...
It's not true! It can't be!
You can't die! Not like this!
A tree? How?
How?
It's so... huge!
I know this smell!
That's... the Captain's magic!
No!
Yudo!
Please, goodness!
I'm fine!
You scared me!
Close?
Somehow, we're still alive!
This is Lord Fongens' world tree magic, and he was wounded so severely!
He must have used all the strength he had to save us!
Has anyone seen the Captain?
No way!
No way! There's no way he's been taken!
Survive, Lord Fongens!
Where are the others?
Sheeran?
Sheeran, he's dead!
Oh, no, please, no!
Oh.
An man...
He saved so many of us from dying.
But even his magic couldn't bring back the people who were already dead.
Half of our squad was killed.
Damn it.
I should have been stronger.
Run!
静かにそっと
ほら新たな日々が始まる
胸にしまい込んだままの
想いを解き放って
その翼を広げて
今飛び立て
あの海原を見下ろして
誰よりも遠く
何度でも
Will you fly?
beautiful
どんな景色も
君といれば輝くよ
だからずっとそばにいて
and never let go
僕のこの手を
離れよ
離さないで
どこまでも
ついてきてほしい
The world is so beautiful
This is only the prologue.
Once our objective comes to fruition
all of you will be plunged into profound misery.
Black Clover page 162
The Great War breaks out.
.
LINE
本質問
FIS
日本